<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon id="skin.amber" version="2.2.3" name="Amber" provider-name="Jester, Pecinko">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.gui" version="5.10.0"/>
    <import addon="script.favourites" version="6.0.3"/>
    <import addon="service.skin.widgets" version="0.0.31"/>
    <import addon="resource.uisounds.amber" version="1.0.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension
    point="xbmc.gui.skin" debugging="false">
    <res width="1920" height="1080" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="1080i" />
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="cs_CZ">Nic zbytečného, jenom vaše media a snadné ovládání</summary>
    <summary lang="de_DE">Keine Bloatware, nur Ihre Medien mit einer leicht zu navigierenden Oberfläche</summary>
    <summary lang="en_AU">No bloatware, just your media with an easy to navigate interface</summary>
    <summary lang="en_GB">No bloatware, just your media with an easy to navigate interface</summary>
    <summary lang="en_NZ">No bloatware, just your media with an easy to navigate interface</summary>
    <summary lang="en_US">No bloatware, just your media with an easy to navigate interface</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_FR">Pas d'usine à gaz, juste les médias avec une interface épurée</summary>
    <summary lang="it_IT">Skin leggera, i tuoi media con un'interfaccia semplice in cui navigare</summary>
    <summary lang="ko_KR">블로트웨어가 아닙니다. 쉬운 탐색 인터페이스를 가진 사용자의 미디어 자체입니다.</summary>
    <summary lang="lt_LT">Nieko nereikalingo, tik jūsų media įrašai ir lengvai valdoma vartotojo sąsaja</summary>
    <summary lang="ms_MY">Tiada perisian palsu, hanya media anda dengan antaramuka yang mudah dinavigasi</summary>
    <summary lang="nb_NO">Ingen tunge og unødvendige funksjoner, bare dine media og ett lettvint grensesnitt</summary>
    <summary lang="nl_NL">Geen bloatware, alleen jouw media met gemakkelijk te navigeren omgeving</summary>
    <summary lang="pl_PL">Bez zbędnych funkcji, tylko Twoje media z łatwym w nawigacji interfejsem.</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Sem bloatware, apenas sua mídia com uma interface fácil de navegar</summary>
    <summary lang="sl_SI">Brez napihnjenega programja, zgolj vaši mediji z vmesnikom, enostavnim za krmarjenje.</summary>
    <description lang="cs_CZ">No bloatware, just your media with an easy to navigate interface[CR] Použité některé textury z projektů Mediastream a Aeon.</description>
    <description lang="de_DE">Keine Bloatware, nur Ihre Medien mit einer einfach zu navigierenden Oberfläche.[CR]Benutzt Texturen aus den Mediastream und Aeon skins.</description>
    <description lang="en_AU">No bloatware, just your media with an easy to navigate interface.[CR]Uses some textures from Mediastream and Aeon skins.</description>
    <description lang="en_GB">No bloatware, just your media with an easy to navigate interface.[CR]Uses some textures from Mediastream and Aeon skins.</description>
    <description lang="en_NZ">No bloatware, just your media with an easy to navigate interface.[CR]Uses some textures from Mediastream and Aeon skins.</description>
    <description lang="en_US">No bloatware, just your media with an easy to navigate interface.[CR]Uses some textures from Mediastream and Aeon skins.</description>
    <description lang="es_ES">Sin complicaciones, sólo tu multimedia en un interfaz sencillo.[CR]Utiliza algunas texturas de los skins Mediastream y Aeon.</description>
    <description lang="fr_CA">Pas d'inflagiciel, juste vos médias avec une interface facile à naviguer.[CR]Utilise des textures des habillages Mediastream et Aeon.</description>
    <description lang="fr_FR">Pas d'utilisation excessive des ressources, juste vos médias avec une interface facile à utiliser.[CR]Utilise quelques textures provenant des habillages Mediastream et Aeon.</description>
    <description lang="he_IL">מעטפת קלילה וללא רכיבים מיותרים, מאפשרת הצגת המדיה עם ממשק משתמש פשוט לניווט.[CR]משתמשת במאפייני עיצוב מסוימים מהמעטפות Mediastream ו־Aeon.</description>
    <description lang="hu_HU">Semmi pazarlás. csak média könnyű kezelhetőséggel és navigációval.[CR]Néhány textúra a Mediastream és Aeon felszínből származik.</description>
    <description lang="it_IT">Skin leggera, i tuoi media con un'interfaccia semplice in cui navigare.[CR]Usa alcuni elementi grafici delle skin Mediastream e Aeon.</description>
    <description lang="ko_KR">블로트웨어가 아닌 그냥 쉬운 탐색 인터페이스를 가진 사용자의 미디어입니다.[CR]Mediastream 과 Aeon 스킨의 텍스처를 사용하였습니다.</description>
    <description lang="lt_LT">Neapkrauta, lengvai valdoma sąsaja. [CR] Naudoja kai kuriuos elementus iš Mediastream and Aeon temų.</description>
    <description lang="ms_MY">Bukan perisian palsu, hanya media anda dengan antaramuka yang mudah dinavigasi.[CR]Gunakan beberapa tekstur dari kulit Mediastream dan Aeon.</description>
    <description lang="nb_NO">Ingen tunge og unødvendige funksjoner, bare dine media og ett lettvint grensesnitt.[CR]Noen teksturer er hentet fra Mediastream og Aeon skallene.</description>
    <description lang="nl_NL">Geen Bloatware. alleen jouw media met een makkelijk te navigeren interface.[CR] gebruikt sommige texturen van Mediastream en Aeon ontwerp.</description>
    <description lang="pl_PL">Bez bezużytecznych funkcji, tylko Twoje media z łatwym w nawigacji interfejsem.[CR] Wykorzystuje niektóre tekstury skóry Mediastream i Aeon</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">Sem excessos, apenas a sua mídia com uma interface fácil de navegar. [CR]Utiliza algumas texturas das skins Mediastream e Aeon.</description>
    <description lang="pt_PT">Um tema sem excessos que apenas mostra a sua média com uma interface de navegação simples.[CR]Utiliza algumas texturas dos temas Mediastream e Aeon.</description>
    <description lang="ru_RU">Никаких вирусов, только ваши медиа файлы в простом интерфейсе.[CR]Использует некоторые текстуры из тем Mediastream и Aeon.</description>
    <description lang="sl_SI">Brez nepotrebnega, le vaše medijske datoteke z enostavnim vmesnikom.[CR]Uporablja nekatere teksture iz tem Mediastream in Aeon.</description>
    <description lang="sv_SE">Inget överflödigt, bara dina media med enkelt navigeringsinterface.[CR]Använder texturer från skalen Mediastream och Aeon.</description>
    <description lang="zh_CN">没有花里胡哨的东西，只是你的媒体和易于浏览的界面。[CR]使用了一些来自 Mediastream 和 Aeon 皮肤的纹理材料.</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 3, June 2007</license>
    <forum>http://forum.kodi.tv/forumdisplay.php?fid=203</forum>
    <source>https://github.com/jester-xbmc/skin.amber</source>
  </extension>
</addon>
